爸爸.
Daddy.
利兰.
Leland.
爸爸.
Daddy.
利兰.
Leland.
爸爸. 爸爸. 利兰.
Daddy. Daddy. Leland.
利兰.
Leland.
Yeah.
啊.
You have the right to an attorney.
你有权请律师.
l waive that right.
我放弃这个权利.
l'm gonna ask you some questions.
我会问你一些问题.
Anything you say may be held
against you in a court of law.
你所说的一切
将会成为呈堂证供.
Do you understand?
明白了?
Yes, of course, l do.
明白, 我当然明白.
On Friday morning, March 3rd,
3月3日, 周五早晨,
did you go
to Calhoun Memorial Hospital?
你有没有
卡尔霍恩纪念医院?
Yes.
去过.
Why did you go there?
你去那里干什么?
l was looking for someone.
我去探病.
Who were you looking for?
探谁?
The man who killed my daughter.
那个杀了我女儿的人.
Did you know his name?
你知道他的名字吗?
No.
不.
Yes. l do now.
啊. 我现在知道了.
Jacques Renault.
雅克·雷诺.
What made you think
he killed Laura?
你怎么知道是
他杀了劳拉?
You arrested him.
因为你逮捕了他.
Leland...
利兰...
...did you kill Jacques Renault?
...是你杀了雅克·雷诺吗?
He killed my Laura.
他杀了我的劳拉.
Have you ever experienced
你们体验过这种
absolute loss?
绝对的痛失吗?
l doubt that any one of us
is a stranger to grief.
恐怕我们之中
都不曾有过如此的悲痛.
No, more than grief.
不, 那不单只是悲痛.
lt's deep down.
而是内心.
lnside.
最深处.
Every cell screams.
每个细胞都在尖叫.
You can hear...
除此之外...
...nothing else.
...再听不见别的.
Yes.
是.
l ki--
我--
l killed him.
杀了他.
Yes.
是的.
Yes, yes, yes.
是, 是, 是.
Yes.
是的.
- He'll plead temporary insanity.
- We'll need a psychiatric exam.
- 暂时先把他界定为精神失常.
- 我们需要做个心理检查.
l'll tell you one thing,
parents should not bury their children.
我想告诉你,
父母真不应该亲眼看着自己的孩子下葬.
Anyone who's been through
what Leland has is--
换作是任何人
像利兰这样--
Do you approve of murder,
Dr. Hayward?
那谋杀是对的囉,
海沃德医生?
No.
不.
Hey, doc.
嗨, 医生.
- How are you, Andy?
- Fine.
- 你好吗, 安迪?
- 还行.
Great. Fine.
很好. 好.
What's the problem?
有问题?
lt's kind of personal.
私人问题.
l'm your doctor, Andy.
我是你的医生, 安迪.
lt's about my sperms test.
是关于我的精子化验.
Yes?
怎么了?
You know, l flunked.
你知道, 我的精不行.
That's not the precise term for it.
也没那么绝对.
Well, l was just wondering
那好, 我在想
if it's the kind of test
you can take over.
你是否可以
帮我在做一次化验.
You know, like a driver's exam.
知道吗, 像司机做的那种.
l mean, l've been wearing boxer shorts
every day just like you told me.
我是说, 我已经按你说的
每天只穿平脚裤.
You wanna give it another shot?
你想再来一炮?
Yes, sir. l would.
是的, 先生. 就这意思.
l'll need to take a sample with me.
那我要带个样本回去.
- Right now?
- Put it in a brown bag.
- 马上?
- 放在棕色的袋子里.
l'll wait in the car.
我在车上等你.
Lucy, l've got
a garbage truck here on...
露西, 我这边
有一台垃圾车正在...
Oh, shut up.
噢, 闭嘴.
Our judge arrives this afternoon.
我们镇的法官下午回到.
Clinton Sternwood.
克林顿·斯登伍.
Travels the circuit in a Winnebago.
东部温尼贝戈地区他都走个遍了.
Outdoors enthusiast?
越野爱好者?
Last of the frontiersmen.
终极拓荒者.
They broke the mold.
这方土地都是他们开发的.
l only got bail hearing for Leland
and Leo's competency examination.
而我只有利兰和里欧的
保释听证会.
Will Leland get bail?
利兰可以保释吗?
Well, Harry, that's up to
your state prosecutor.
嗯, 哈里, 那就要看
你这儿的检察官了.
That'd be Daryl Lodwick.
检察官叫达里尔·罗威克.
Also on his way.
也在来的路上了.
When do we hear from Hawk?
豪克那边有消息吗?
He called this morning.
他今早打过电话来.
Now, the county...
现在, 县里...
...说没有一个
叫罗伯逊的人
...says nobody
by the name of Robertson
在帕尔默家
旁边住过.
had ever lived
next to the Palmers.
我们拿到最后一个房客
的现住址了.
We got a current address
on the last occupants.
在蒙大拿州的卡列斯佩尔.
Kalispell.
下午前派人过去查.
We'll check it by afternoon.
- 嘿. 看着点, 安迪.
- 对不起, 鲍勃.
- Hey. Watch it, Andy.
- Sorry, Bob.
噢, 我的天啊.
Oh, my God.
安迪, 别动.
Andy, don't move.
- 你在哪里搞到这个的?
- 别逼我说
- Where did you get those?
- Don't make me say
到底从哪儿来的.
where these came from.
安迪?
Andy?
别问了, 库珀探员,
这个绝对是个人隐私.
Please, Agent Cooper,
this is extremely personal business.
你的靴子?
Your boots?
噢, 不好意思.
Oh, l'm sorry.
昨天菲利普·杰勒德在等你们时
我帮他买的. 真抱歉.
l bought these from Phillip Gerard
yesterday when he was waiting. Sorry.
和里欧的那双
是一个牌子.
These are the same brand of boots
we found at Leo Johnson's.
巨人说
线索会在这里出现.
The Giant said
there was a clue out there.
我还以为是可卡因呢?
l thought it was the cocaine?
哈里, 一定要找到菲利普·杰勒德,
独臂人.
Harry, we've gotta find Phillip Gerard,
the one-armed man.
我可以走了吗, 库珀探员?
Can l go now, Agent Cooper?
我赶时间.
l don't know how much time l've got.
你赶,先走吧.
lf you must.
哈里, 露西怎么了?
Harry, what's with Lucy?
- 荷恩先生.
- 边走边说.
- Mr. Horne.
- Walk and talk.
我一个在西雅图派邮件
的朋友.
This friend of mine works
with the Seattle Post-Dispatch.
其实, 她是我妹的大学校友
但也算是我的朋友了.
Actually, my sister went to college
with her but she's a friend of mine too.
反正, 她今早打电话来报了个
猛料. 最高机密.
Anyway, she called me this morning
with a hot tip. Top secret.
安·提·文思要来
双峰镇了.
M.T. Wentz is coming
to Twin Peaks.
安·提·文思, 安·提·文思.
M.T. Wentz. M.T. Wentz.
安·提·文思, 那个游记作家.
M.T. Wentz, the travel writer.
对, 安·提·文思, 游记作家.
Yes, M.T. Wentz the travel writer.
文思出行从来不用真名,
和信用卡, 只付现金.
Wentz travels incognito,
uses only cash, no credit cards.
所以没有人知道他到底是谁.
Nobody can trace his identity.
也许是女的. 报纸上也从没说
这人是男是女.
Or hers. No one at the paper
even knows who he or she is.
有价值,文思的到访
或许有利我们酒店宣传.
Favorable Wentz review
could be quite useful.
就是, 他快来了.
快要来了, 快要来了.
Well, he's coming.
He's coming, he's coming.
你给我在前台盯着.
每小时更新一次信息.
Keep an eye on the registration.
l want an hourly update.
- 仔细核对每一张单据.
- 特别是付现金的.
- Scrutinize every check.
- Especially if they pay cash.
还没到9:30下班
你就已经做好了一天的工作了.
Not even 9:30 and you have
already done a good day's work.
荷恩先生.
Mr. Horne.
你气色不错啊.
You look well.
- 有什么可以帮你吗?
- 哦, 我们见过.
- What can l do for you?
- Oh, we've met.
我推销小企业
保险业务.
l sell insurance
to the small business.
像独眼杰克赌场.
Like One-Eyed Jack.
尚·雷诺.
Jean Renault.
有何贵干?
What's the occasion?
我的保险费
又涨价了?
Are my premiums
about to be raised?
不, 不. 不是那样的.
No, no. Nothing like that.
请坐.
Please.
你这个浑蛋.
You bastard.
- 你这个浑蛋!
- 先别误会, 荷恩先生.
- You bastard!
- Make no mistake, Mr. Horne.
我只是来传话的.
l'm just the messenger.
帮谁传?
From whom?
他们要一大笔赎金.
They request a large sum of money.
多少?
How much?
我还有其他要求.
l require something else entirely.
他们应该承担
中介费.
They should bear the cost
of their own middleman.
第一.
Number one.
你那里的生意
Your business up there
已经慢慢给那些
吃里扒外的庸才侵蚀.
is being run
by pickpockets and fools.
赚到的钱左手进右手出.
A dollar earned is a dollar stolen.
你注意到了吗?
Are you aware of that?
我早就怀疑了.
l have my suspicions.
你需要一个合伙人.
What you need is a partner.
一个可以帮你
处理这些琐事的人.
Someone who can take care
of these little problems.
- 我已经有合伙人了.
- 那好.
- l have a partner.
- Okay.
那你到底想不想我帮你?
Do you want my help or no?
想.
Yes.
还有一个.
One more thing.
我要这个人
带赎金过来.
l want this man
to bring to me the ransom.
这个人是联邦调查局的探员.
This man is an FBl agent.
你想赎回你女儿吗?
Do you want your daughter back?
这当然, 我当然想赎回女儿
但我不能--
Of course, l want my daughter back
but l can't--
现金...
Cash...
...合伙人...
...partner...
...探员.
...FBl man.
这个交易
还真划算.
This is supposed to be
an equitable exchange.
顺其自然就好.
This could turn out well.
那明天等你电话...
Expect a call tomorrow...
...中午.
...noon.
珍妮特.
Janet.
快给我找库珀探员.
急事.
Find Agent Cooper for me.
lt's urgent.
你开玩笑吧?
You're kidding?
他长得怎样?
What's he look like?
哇, 唐娜,
你今天好漂亮.
Well, you're looking
real pretty today, Donna.
- 谢谢.
- 约会吗?
- Thanks.
- Special occasion?
对. 送餐时认识的
约了他一起吃午饭.
Yeah. l'm having lunch today
with someone l met on my route.
老尿壶和自闭症.
有什么好约会的?
Bedpans and shut-ins.
Who's to meet?
你不会理解的.
You wouldn't understand.
- 别把汤洒了.
- 谢了, 路易.
- Don't spill the soup.
- Thanks, Louie.
嘿, 有好消息.
Hey, listen to this.
北方酒店的那个路易
刚给我打了电话.
l just got a call from Louie
at the Northern.
安·提·文思
要来双峰镇了.
M.T. Wentz is coming
to Twin Peaks.
菩提·肉丝是谁?
Empty who?
汉克, 他是我国最有威望的
一个美食评论家.
Hank, he's the most powerful
restaurant critic in the state.
- 真的?
- 是啊.
- Really?
- Yeah.
如果他能在西雅图邮报
上为我们美言几句
And a good review
from him and his Seattle paper
那我们双食店就火了.
could give us a lot of business.
路易说会想办法
介绍他过来吃饭.
So she's gonna try to
send him our way.
他长什么样子?
What's he look like?
这个, 每人见过.
我猜是个秘密.
Well, nobody knows.
l guess it's a secret.
但估计他
今天就会到.
But he's supposed to be
arriving today.
那我们还有时间.
Then we still got time.
有什么时间, 汉克?
Time for what, Hank?
我要去采些花回来
l'm gonna pick up some flowers
还有漂亮的蜡烛
和桌布.
and maybe some candles
and some tablecloths.
菜牌上你看再加点什么菜式?
特别点的.
And what can we add to the menu?
Some specials maybe.
我一直都想
加些地方小菜了.
l always wanted to try
some regional dishes.
宝贝, 我们要把这里打扮得漂漂亮亮
就像过圣诞和国庆一样.
Babe, we're gonna trick this place out
like Christmas on the Fourth of July.
噢, 我觉得
你应该打个电话给大个儿艾德.
Oh, and l think
you should give Big Ed a call.
- 为什么?
- 嗯...
- Why?
- Well...
...你们不是好朋友吗, 对吧?
...you're still friendly, right?
那个文思可能
会停在那儿加油.
So maybe this Wentz guy
stops in for gas.
要是艾德见到陌生人
叫他通知一声.
Ed could suggest the Double R
to any new faces he sees.
- 我会跟他说的.
- 好.
- l'll call him.
- Good.
记住了.
You do that.
那么...
So...
...为什么干杯好呢?
...what shall we drink to?
为劳拉.
To Laura.
铭刻心中.
ln our hearts and memories, locked.
她的日记.
Her diary.
我告诉过你她日记的事吗?
Did l tell you l had it?
劳拉的日记?
Laura's diary?
我给你读一段怎样?
Shall l read something from it?
今天似乎很合适.
lt seems appropriate.
读吧.
Please.
"但我还是不敢告诉她
我的美梦和恶梦.
''But still l'm afraid to tell her
of my fantasies and my nightmares.
有时她会
理解我说的.
Sometimes she's good
at understanding.
但大多数时候她都会笑话我
而我也没有这个勇气告诉她
Other times she just giggles
and l don't have the nerve to ask
真搞不懂她听了
有什么会觉得好笑.
why things like that
are funny to her.
我却感觉遭透了
所以我很长一段时间没再提起.
So l feel badly again
and shut up about it for a long time.
我是那么的爱唐娜--
l love Donna very mu--
但有时我又很害怕
她再也不在我身边了
But sometimes l worry that
she wouldn't be around me at all
她知道我内心的
困扰吗.
if she knew what my insides
were like.
暗黑的力量
渗透了我的梦...
Black and dark
and soaked with dreams of...
...那,那高个儿男人也许会
想方设法捉到我
...big, big men and different ways
that they might hold me
和控制我."
and take me into their control.''
对不起.
l'm sorry.
别, 别这样说.
No, don't be.
嗯-- 我只是觉得, 我是说--
l-- l was just, l mean--
我是说, 这也算是证据,
我们不是应该交给警方吗?
l mean, if that's evidence,
shouldn't we give that to the sheriff?
不.
No.
我意思是...
l mean...
我-- 我已经
从头到尾看过了, 唐娜,
l've-- l've read this
from cover to cover, Donna,
里面没有答案.
and there are no solutions here.
而且...
Besides...
...是她给我的东西.
...she gave it to me.
为什么?
Why?
人们来我这里
讲他们的故事
People come to me
and tell me their stories
他们在外面的故事.
about the world outside.
我聆听
并用文字
l take their stories
and place them
记录下来.
in a larger context.
再整理成小说.
A sort of living novel.
谁和你讲故事?
Who tells you?
噢, 朋友.
Oh, friends.
爱人.
Lovers.
嗯, 或许, 某天, 你也愿意讲.
Well, maybe, someday, you will too.
给你说中了.
You were right.
那些绑匪今天上午
联系我了.
Her kidnappers contacted me
this morning.
我真该死, 而你是对的.
Damn me, but you were right.
你为什么不报警?
Why didn't you alert the sheriff?
如果警方介入,他们会立刻杀了她
所以我才找你来.
They'll kill her at first sign of police
involvement. That's why l called you.
但这不是理由来规避
正常的办案渠道.
That's no reason to circumvent
normal channels.
按常规办案
我女儿就没法活着回来了.
Normal channels won't bring
my daughter back to me alive.
你和欧蕊...
You and Audrey...
关系特别.
You have a special relationship.
你, 所有人,
You, of all people,
都知道她对我多重要.
understand her value to me.
他们明天
就要赎金.
They wanna make
the exchange tomorrow.
欧蕊...
Audrey...
...12万5千美金.
...for $1 25,000.
现金.
Cash.
但我请求你.
But l must ask you.
你能送钱过去吗?
Will you take it there?
乔西.
Josie.
噢, 皮特.
Oh, Pete.
我真难过.
So sorry.
是, 我也是.
Yeah, me too.
你知道, 我...
You know, l...
...老是想起安德鲁.
...keep thinking about Andrew.
如果他在会怎样处理
这次火灾.
What he would have done
about the fire.
谢天谢地还有凯瑟琳
在这里处理.
Thank goodness Catherine was here
to handle everything.
怎么了?
What is it?
乔西,
Josie,
凯瑟琳烧死了.
Catherine died in the fire.
上帝, 不会的.
God, no.
噢, 皮特.
Oh, Pete.
我们...
We're...
我们要准备葬礼了...
We're planning a service...
...但他们还没找到尸体.
...but they haven't found the body.
哦, 皮特.
Oh, Pete.
过两天就要举行了.
ln a couple of days we'll go ahead.
我还真不知道
到时候葬什么.
l don't know exactly
what we'll be burying.
这边. 过来,
游魂鬼. 爸爸来接你了.
Right this way. Come on,
dreamboat. Daddy's waiting.
快来.
Come on.
荷恩小姐真不乖,
什么要都不吃.
Miss Horne was a very bad girl,
refusing to take her medicine.
- 请别.
- 没错吧, 荷恩小姐?
- Please.
- Weren't you, Miss Horne?
欧蕊?
Audrey?
欧蕊,
Audrey,
有人虐待你吗?
have you been mistreated?
他打我.
He hit me.
我没打她.
l did not hit her.
别听她说, 我没有.
lf that's what you're thinking, l didn't.
那就不对了.
That was wrong.
只要你和我在一起
就再也不会发生了.
lt will never happen again
as long as you're with me.
你明白了?
Do you understand?
我今早和你爸爸
谈过了.
l spoke with your father
this morning.
你不会有危险的.
You're in no danger.
事情进行得很顺利.
Everything going to be fine.
相信我.
You do trust me.
你会的, 欧蕊?
Don't you, Audrey?
你看, 欧蕊,
You see, Audrey,
现在这情形,
in a situation like this,
你要管好自己
友善点.
you have to handle yourself
in a professional manner.
我们都是明白人
至于你知道的那些事
We're all reasonable people
and what you discover
明白人做明白事
我们可以坐下来
is that something reasonable
can always be worked out
慢慢谈
我们会理解的--
whenever reasonable people
just put their minds--
别哭.
No.
露西?
Lucy?
露西, 我们要谈谈.
Lucy, we need to talk.
布伦南副警长,
Deputy Brennan,
我想你更应该
和你的色情杂志谈去?
l thought you preferred
the company of your magazine?
安迪?
Andy?
你还是先出去透透气吧.
Maybe you'd better get some air.
露西,
Lucy,
如果有什么困扰着你
不如说出来我听听
l think we're at the point where
it would be healthier for everyone
找出问题, 这样
对大家都有好处.
if you got whatever was
bothering you out in the open.
安迪和我以前谈过恋爱.
Andy and l used to go out.
这个我知道.
That much l gathered.
一起有一年半了,我开始发觉他
有点不对劲.
For a year and a half until l started
to notice things about him.
也不是什么大事,
就是些小毛病.
They weren't big things,
they were little things.
他从不运动.
He never exercises.
从不洗自己的车
甚至连一套运动服也没有.
He never washes his car
and he doesn't even own a sports coat.
那, 你有没有做些什么
去改善他?
Well, did you do
something about this?
嗯, 在我看完电视后,
我决定要给自己一些时间
Well, after l watched this TV show,
l decided l needed some me time
那段时间里
我们不再见面.
during which
we didn't see each other.
正在那时
我遇到了基巴·翠梅恩.
During which period
l met Dick Tremayne.
荷恩百货店,
男装部的.
Horne's Department Store,
Men's Fashions.
他有好多大衣,而且他自己和车都
总是保持得干净有型.
He had lots of coats and keeps himself
and his car in great shape.
虽然他的举止像只蠢驴,
Most of his behavior was asinine,
但总算和别人不一样.
but at least he was different.
你现在还有和这个基巴来往吗?
Are you still seeing this Dick?
没有了.
No.
露西, 你想和安迪
和好吗?
Lucy, do you wanna get
back together with Andy?
我不知道.
l don't know.
那好, 露西, 你能准确告诉我
你到底想要什么吗?
Well, Lucy, can you tell me exactly
what you do want?
我就是不知道.
l don't know.
没办法, 哈里, 真想帮帮她.
Sorry, Harry, l was trying to help.
嗯, 有心就好.
Well, it was a good thought.
但有些事就像
9号高速上的那个大坑一样.
But it's like trying to fix
those potholes over on Highway 9.
一场大雨过后就...
First heavy rain and...
你开过那条路?
You've been down this road before?
当然开过.
Sure have.
哈里.
Harry.
我现在的情况很危险.
l've got a dangerous situation.
我已经仔细考量过每一种可能性
l've examined every possible angle
我相信
现在只有一条路能行得通.
and l believe
there's only one way to proceed.
帮我个忙, 但只能你知道.
l need a favor, strictly between us.
出什么事了?
What's up?
我需要一个书屋会的人.
最棒的那个.
l need one of the Bookhouse Boys.
Your best man.
可以的话
先别问我为什么.
lt would be better
if you didn't know why.
库珀, 只要你开口
我会照办的.
Cooper, l've steered clear
when you asked me to.
还有什么需要
交待我的吗?
ls there anything l need to know
about this one?
没有了.
Absolutely not.
我会安排的.
l'll set it up.
9点半在公路旅社见.
Nine-thirty at the Roadhouse.
谢谢, 哈里.
Thanks, Harry.
- 肯定是他.
- 来了.
- lt must be him.
- Here we go.
晚上好, 先生,
欢迎光临双食店.
Good evening, sir,
welcome to the Double R Diner.
谢谢, 可以要卡座吗?
Thanks, could l have a booth?
没问题, 这边请.
Of course, right this way.
今晚我们有2款
特别美食精选--
We have two very delicious
specials this evening--
不用了,给我来份
半熟芝士汉堡,
l'm sure you do but l'll have
a cheeseburger, medium,
可乐和薯条.
a Coke and some fries.
好的.
Very good.
不好意思, 陶德?
Excuse me, Toad?
不如我们到厨房
那边去吃吧.
Why don't we finish this up
in the kitchen?
There you go.
吃完收拾好
别乱碰东西.
Get in the back
and don't touch anything.
他只点了芝士汉堡.
He only wanted a cheeseburger.
那肯定是美食评论家
的个人癖好.
lt must be some kind of
food-critic trick.
- 你觉得是吗?
- 绝对是, 呀. 我想--
- You think so?
- Absolutely, yeah. l think--
洗手间?
Bathroom?
哦, 这边请, 先生.
Oh, right this way, sir.
我们刚刚装修完
感觉很好的.
We just finished painting it
and it looks really nice.
独立单格都有门的的.
是, 跟我来.
lt's completely private.
Yeah, follow me.
哦, 对不起.
Oh, sorry.
- 好东西.
- 陶德!
- Good stuff.
- Toad!
陶德, 快给我出来...
Toad, get out of my...
谢谢你能来见我.
Thanks for coming.
- 我不知道...
- 什么?
- l didn't know...
- Know what?
我不知道你受了什么刺激.
l didn't know if you were mad or not.
我是说, 也许真刺激了你.
l mean, how mad.
我受得了.
l'll survive.
唐娜, 我和詹姆斯之间
真的没有什么.
Donna, there's nothing going on
between me and James.
有又怎样呢? 我是说,
What if there is? l mean,
谁规定我或詹姆斯
不能和别人约会了?
who said James and l
couldn't see other people?
我肯定不会.
l certainly didn't.
你意思是你也在
和别人约会吗?
Are you saying you're seeing
someone else?
马蒂, 我需要你帮忙.
Maddy, l need your help.
- 怎么帮?
- 哈罗德·史密斯有劳拉的日记.
- How?
- Harold Smith has Laura's diary.
警察不是已经
有劳拉的日记了吗.
l thought the sheriff
had Laura's diary.
哈罗德说劳拉还有第二本日记
我们不知道的
Harold said that Laura kept
a second diary that l didn't know about
在他那儿.
and he's got it.
天啊.
God.
我们要告诉詹姆斯.
We have to tell James about this.
如果劳拉真还有秘密日记...
lf Laura did have a secret diary...
...而且在哈罗德那儿...
...and Harold's got it...
...我一定要拿到它
你到底帮不帮我.
...l'm gonna get it
with or without you.
你告诉詹姆斯去
Tell that to James.
我知道我花太多钱买它了,
l know l paid too much for it,
但我真爱死它了.
but l just fell in love with it.
知道那个售货员怎么说吗,
l heard the salesperson say,
"我们还在经营
的唯一原因就是
''The only reason
we're still in business
因为乔西·帕卡德
来这里购物."
is because Josie Packard
buys retail.''
我喜欢.
l like it.
- 真的吗?
- 我喜欢, 真的.
- You do?
- l like it, yeah.
- 你摸起来好冷.
- 乔西.
- You're so cold.
- Josie.
乔西, 我想知道.
你真的去了西雅图吗?
Josie, l gotta know.
Were you really in Seattle?
是啊, 你什么时候变的那么多疑了?
Yes, why are you so suspicious?
看这些礼盒.
Look at these boxes.
你以为我是
在这里买的吗?
You think l got them
at Cash and Carry?
那你为什么不告诉我一声
就走了?
Why didn't you tell me
you were going?
你知道我必须避开,
我好怕.
You know l had to get away,
l was afraid.
- 我明白, 你怕本和凯瑟琳.
- 你知道的.
- l know, afraid of Ben and Catherine.
- You know that.
但是凯瑟琳现在已经死了.
And now Catherine's dead.
哈里?
Harry?
- 你不会以为是我--
- 我也不知道自己在想什么.
- You don't think l--
- l don't know what to think.
- 我真不知道.
- 你以为是我烧了锯木厂?
- l don't know.
- You think l could burn the mill?
我会亲手毁了
自己的东西?
That l would ruin
everything of mine?
保险金啊.
There's insurance money.
我的天啊.
My God.
你竟然?
How could you?
你竟然把我想的
那么恶毒?
How could you think
of such terrible things?
竟然这样来伤我的心?
How could you hurt me so?
我只不过太焦虑了.
l was just so worried.
很对不起.
l'm sorry.
抱着我.
Hold me.
- 要我.
- 乔西.
- Take me.
- Josie.
- 我好想你要我.
- 乔西.
- l want you to take me.
- Josie.
乔西, 为什么?
为什么你告诉我呢?
Josie, why?
Why didn't you tell me?
撕开它.
Tear it.
什么?
What?
撕开它.
Tear it.
我好想要你.
l want you.
我需要你.
l need you.
我想要你
l want you
胜过我自己的生命.
more than my own life.
嗨, 美媚.
Hi, good-looking.
你不给我来杯好咖啡
慰劳一下嘛?
Who do you have to grease
to get some coffee around here?
斯登伍法官.
你好, 法官大人.
Judge Sternwood.
Hello, Your Honor.
露西, 你干嘛
Lucy, you're a cool drink of water
两眼泪汪汪的.
to road-weary eyes.
藏着什么秘密呢?
What's your secret?
还是别提了它, 先生.
l'd rather not talk about it, sir.
那我们来抱抱吧?
Give us a hug?
生活艰难啊, 亲爱的.
Life is hard, dear.
尽管如此, 还是要...
Still and all, it's...
要知道还有很多地方
比双峰镇过的艰难多了.
lt's harder in most places
than in Twin Peaks.
克林顿.
Clinton.
不好意思,我来晚了.
Sorry l'm late.
哦, 我也是刚到.
Oh, l only just arrived.
见到你真好.
Good to see you.
她叫什么, 哈里?
What's her name, Harry?
- 啊?
- 你好像刚刚驯完
- What?
- You got the look of a man
一匹小母马, 我的儿.
with filly trouble, son.
如果它们不愿意上鞍,
那你有2个选择.
lf they don't take the saddle,
you got two options.
- 一定有一个能奏效.
- 哈里?
- And l won't bore you with either one.
- Harry?
斯登伍法官,
特别探员戴尔·库珀.
Judge Sternwood,
Special Agent Dale Cooper.
联邦调查局.
FBl.
- 你好么,小伙子?
- 你好,法官大人.
- How are you, lad?
- Your Honor.
你们2个
有很多共同点.
You two should have
a lot in common.
希很快就会把法庭日程表带来
Sid will bring in the court calendar
像醉倒北印第安人
那么快.
as soon as the Winnebago
is tanked up.
你想看你在爱尔兰帮我
收藏的那封密信吗?
You wanna break the seal
on that lrish you stashed for me?
这边谈.
Right this way.
库珀先生, 你是怎么找到
我们这个小地方的?
Mr. Cooper, how do you find
our little corner of this world?
这里美的像天堂, 先生.
Heaven, sir.
嗯, 这周, 天堂发生了
Well, this week, heaven includes
纵火案, 多起谋杀案
arson, multiple homicides
还差点要了
联邦探员的名.
and an attempt on the life
of a federal agent.
天堂是个总是给人
意外的大地方, 先生.
Heaven is a large
and interesting place, sir.
露西?
Lucy?
基巴.
Dick.
露西, 我寝不宁.
Lucy, l haven't slept.
食不安.
l can't eat.
一直沉浸在巨大的痛苦之中.
l've been absolutely miserable.
你有么?
You have?
我觉得自己卑鄙,无耻,下流,愚蠢至极,
我所做的让我觉得...
l've been a fool, a cad,
the way l've behaved and l'm...
极其, 极其羞耻.
l'm deeply, deeply ashamed.
是吗?
You are?
我已经在脑海里反覆
挣扎过百万次了
l've been over it in my mind
a million times
所以我终于来了.
and what l've come to is this.
我不得不--
l have to--
不, 我必须要做出正确的事了.
No, l must do the right thing.
你必须?
You must?
是--
lt's--
我决定把一切都
结束了.
lt's everything l could
scrape together.
我真的筋疲力尽了.
l'm completely knackered.
这是什么?
What is this?
6百50美元.
Six hundred and fifty dollars.
我打电话咨询过了.
l've called around.
这些钱
足够有余了.
l've been told
it's more than adequate.
做什么有余?
For what?
做那个--
For the--
就是处理那个--
To take care of--
你明白的...
You know...
...那个小麻烦.
...the little problem.
理查,
Richard,
你接下来要做的:
here's what you're going to do:
那好你的钱,
Take your money,
放回你的钱包
或口袋里,
put it back in your wallet
or your pocket,
转身起步走, 然后
穿过这两道门--
turn around and walk through
both sets of doors--
第二道有时会有点卡.
The second one sticks sometimes.
--出门直接到停车场,
上车, 启动,
--go out into the parking lot,
get in your car, turn the key,
从今以后, 只要你还活着一天
and never, ever speak to me again
就再也不要来和我说话了!
as long as you live!
你敢再多说一个字我就尖叫.
Say one more word and l'll scream.
滚, 请滚吧.
Leave, please.
基巴!
Dick!
基巴.
Dick.
利兰...
Leland...
...我深感遗憾.
...this is most difficult.
对你痛失亲人
My deepest condolences
我表示最深切的慰问.
on your heartbreaking loss.
谢谢你, 先生.
Thank you, sir.
我在法庭见过你
很多次了.
You've appeared before me
many times.
我知道你是一个很好的,
大方得体的人
l know you to be a fine,
decent man
而且是个很有才干的律师.
and a capable attorney.
看到这种事
发生在你身上...
And to see you under
these circumstances is...
我们都很震惊.
ls dreadful for us all.
既然, 法律提供了一个架构
Now, the law provides a structure
指导并引领我们渡过
艰难险阻的时刻.
to guide us through
perilous and trying times.
同时它也要求我们以更坚强的意志
去服从它, 秉公执法.
But it requires our submission
to its procedures and higher purposes.
当我们下定决心要在这场永恒的人间戏剧
里承担各自不同的角色...
Before we assume our respective roles
in this enduring drama...
...我这样说吧
...just let me say that
我们必须鼓起勇气去面对
栖息在我们意志中
when these frail shadows
we inhabit now
最薄弱的阴暗面,
have quit the stage,
相信我们会再次相聚在
we'll meet
死神的瓦尔哈拉神殿
and raise a glass again together
并举杯痛饮.
in Valhalla.
我相信会的.
Would that it were so.
对你提出自辩的请求
我表示理解.
l understand it's your intention
to represent yourself.
是的.
Correct.
那好, 洛威呢,
那个检察官?
Well, where's Lodwick,
the prosecutor?
- 还没到呢.
- 这样吧, 我看
- Overdue.
- Well, l suggest
我们明早再决定
保释的事吧.
we leave the question of bail
till morning.
你对此决定满意吗, 利兰?
The facilities are adequate, Leland?
哦, 满意.
Oh, yes.
每个人对我都非常仁慈.
Everyone has been most kind.
那我们就晚安吧.
Then we'll say good night.
- 副警长.
- 晚安.
- Deputy.
- Good night.
感谢你.
Thank you.
我们这里说吧.
l'll speak for us all.
这事非常棘手.
We have hard jobs.
出庭名单定了.
We're ready to roll.
哇哦, 嗨, 希.
Well, hi, Sid.
哈里.
Harry.
希, 快向特派探员
库珀问好.
Sid, say hello
to Special Agent Cooper.
- 库珀探员,你好.
- 你好吗?
- Agent Cooper.
- How do you do?
那, 先生们,
Well, gentlemen,
我们已经赶了
8小时的路.
we've been eight hours
on the road.
希和我准备挤进
大北方酒店,
Sid and l are gonna pile it over
to The Great Northern,
找上小维尼一起
去大木房里用个美餐.
hook up the Winne
and dine in the Timber Room.
法庭上见.
See you in court.
他妻子?
Wife?
法律秘书.
Law clerk.
好家伙啊.
Man, oh, man.
哈里, 今晚的事都安排好了?
Harry, is everything set for tonight?
都安排妥了.
He'll be there.
好.
Okay.
这是你朋友卡特里娜?
ls this your friend Katrina?
卡特里娜? 卡特里娜.
Katrina? Katrina.
这位小姐叫...
And this is Miss...
这边来, 小姐们.
Come along, girls.
好了, 托吉麻辣先生. 我们都安排好了.
All right, Mr. Tojamura. We're all set.
请问, 你使用什么
信用卡?
Now, what credit card
do you wanna put that on?
- 麻烦你, 我付现金.
- 现金?
- Cash, please.
- Cash?
好的.
Fine.
你刚刚说
你从哪里来, 先生?
Where did you say
you traveled from, sir?
- 西雅图.
- 西雅图?
- Seattle.
- Seattle?
噢, 那, 其实也不是很远.
Oh, that's not such a long trip, then.
很好啊, 托吉麻辣先生.
Very good, Mr. Tojamura.
行李生会把行李直接
送到你房间的.
The bellman will take you
up to your suite.
如果你想在这里
And if you would like to treat yourself
品尝到最地道的
风味菜,
to some of our outstanding
local cuisine while you're here,
我推介你去
双食店.
l would recommend
the Double R Diner.
找诺玛就行了.
Ask for Norma.
非常感谢你.
Thank you very much.
诺玛, 我是路易.
Norma, it's Louie.
目标人物出现了.
l think the eagle has landed.
- 皮特, 见见我表弟乔纳森.
- 乔纳森.
- Pete, meet my cousin Jonathan.
- Jonathan.
你以为表弟叫"乔"吗?
You thinking cousin have some joe?
飞了那么长时间
人物锺都乱了.
After a long flight it will help him
reset his biographical clock.
是 "生物钟."
That's ''biological.''
那也是,我刚好沏了茶.
l think so, l just made a fresh pot.
来. 马上给乔泡一杯.
Here. Cup of joe coming up.
- 生物钟.
- Biological.
真不知道你这6年怎么过的.
Don't know how you lasted six years.
除了乡巴佬和
民工,就没别的了.
Nothing but hayseeds
and manual laborers.
耶, 我们的任务不同嘛.
Well, we all got our job to do.
你的差不多完成了吧.
Yours is nearly finished.
锯木厂和帕卡德的地
都卖出了?
The sale of the mill
and the Packard lands?
合同一签就成了.
我要等皮特签名.
Signing the contracts soon.
l need Pete's signature.
- 他的凯瑟琳的继承人.
- 会很麻烦吗?
- He's Catherine's heir.
- Will that be difficult?
- 不会.
- 要多久?
- No.
- How long?
- 2天.
- 我们计划回香港了.
- Two days.
- We're expected back in Hong Kong.
埃卡先生急着
想见你.
Mr. Eckhardt wants very much
to see you.
还有什么其它变化吗?
Are there any other complications?
汉克那边可能有点难搞.
There might be a problem with Hank.
交给我吧.
l'll deal with him.
- 有人会怀疑我们吗?
- 肯定不会.
- Are we suspected?
- Certainly not.
那个警长呢?
What about this sheriff?
我对他没意思.
He means nothing to me.
我不是问你这个.
That's not what l asked you.
9点半, 不迟不早刚刚好.
Nine-thirty, right on the tick.
他到了吗?
ls he here?
到了.
He's here.
我们有什么急事吗?
Are we in any particular hurry?
哈里,
Harry,
我请你喝杯啤酒. 酒保?
let me buy you a beer. Bartender?
别敲了, 就来了!
All right, l'm coming!
别敲了!
All right!
嘿, 我们还没开--
Hey, we're not op--
哼, 放屁.
Oh, fart.
有啥事啊?
What's the deal?
我认识你吗?
Do l know you?
好了.
Okay.
听着, 我想就这样
躺一会算了.
Listen, l think l'm just gonna
lay here for a while.
怎么回事?
What?
到底咋回事了?
滴血为盟,
下次我会把你头拧下来.
Blood brother,
next time l take your head off.